K
[music]
[Applause]
when we
are in
the
every place. We hold on,
not because
it's too big,
hold on,
please let us go.
If we hold on together,
I know our dreams will never die. You see us through to forever.
Remember,
for each of you, Mother Ho,
remember for love. Stop, the
myriad flowers, the heart, the...
[Applause] my dear, my love, my dear, I am so special.
This morning, Spring is so beautiful, inside and out.
Huyen Nam, I hope you promise, my child, far from home, leaving
spring, I will come back. Sad spring sings on the
field,
sad Spring sings in each person, love.
Spring sings in the heart, calling
love. Spring HT, my love,
[Applause] this life,
this color
[Applause]
together, hand on hand,
people like one,
how can I see your lips
worn when you are sad, sad, where are you, forgetting
everything, forgetting to eat, five years, I remember each of us in a different
place, up again, together in the same direction, love,
there is
Two, three, four,
five, come here, we'll happily divide and talk,
laughing together, shaking hands, no
one will give each other promises. Father and mother
give each other promises,
this love in one house, in this song, come together, go
together, one, two, three, five, brothers,
come together, go together, five, four, three, two, one, let's
pour together, two, we'll drink together, three, let's
drink together, we don't want anyone to be
separated, remember that we're going together,
hand in hand, come home, lie down, don't come home, that's the forest,
salt, the price, the
distant, we go, the fun, the lips, the
hanging, the big,
happy, talking, saying, from the person in the day,
happy, Phu, saying, and the matter, Linh, into the
words, the person, the garden,
for the, climbing up, we'll grill, we'll drink, we'll eat, we'll eat, we'll finish
all the food, oh, the singing, the singing,
no one is hanging, no one is crossing,
H,
H is up, then, the prison, we have to, climb up, the
general, and the corn
Ho Nhat Xong Cho H, a few children, oh, ho,
it's like
no one is resisting, no one is offering food,
ho, it's
H. Sisters, this afternoon we're going
up to let loose, the afternoon is still tense, B,
where
else is the country, it's too much already, already
[Applause]
ch
[Music]
C st hold on to the
end
th
mountain. There is a
fountain washes our tears all
[Music]
a Words is
someone is
Pray. Please let us come home.